[Setup]
AIM Toolkit - Setup
Welcome to the installer for AIM Toolkit.
This will install the AIM Toolkit (build %S).
Installation folder:
 Components 
Arsenal Image Mounter driver (required)
Image File Mounter
RamDisk Configuration Tool
 Options 
Enable entries in context menus
Create shortcuts on desktop
Shortcuts for all users
Language:
Please keep your mouse over an item to get details.
Install driver.##This includes a command line tool, aim_ll.exe, and interfaces to manage volumes from Explorer context menus.
Mount various image file formats like VHD, VDI, VMDK and others.##Installs a command line tool in the installation folder, aim_cli.exe, and a dedicated dialog box to use it from file context menu in Explorer.##Requires .NET Framework 4.8.
This tool will allow you to easily configure one or several RamDisks with various settings.
Add entries in the drive context menu and the file context menu to manage AIM virtual disks and image files directly from Explorer.##This option can be set later in the Windows Start Menu.
Create shortcuts on desktop.##All shortcuts are always created in the Windows Start Menu.
Create shortcuts for all users instead of current user.
Credits
Install
Cancel
Installing...
File copy error.
Invalid path.
Error: driver cannot be installed.
Error: cannot create service.
The previous installation is in another folder.#Do you want to remove it?
Installation finished.
Installation finished.##However, .NET Framework 4.8 is not present on your system.##Please download installer at#<a href="https://dotnet.microsoft.com/download/dotnet-framework/net48">https://dotnet.microsoft.com/download/dotnet-framework/net48</a>
OK

General Settings
Uninstall
Home page
RamDisk Configuration
Mount Image File

Mount as AIM Virtual Disk
Save disk contents as image file
Unmount AIM Virtual Disk


AIM Toolkit - Setup
Uninstall driver (no reboot required)
Remove settings
Reset TEMP variables
Uninstall
Cancel
AIM virtual disk detected.#All existing AIM virtual disks will be unmounted!
Unmounting AIM virtual disks...
Stopping %s...
Removing remaining components...


AIM Toolkit - Setup
 General Settings 
Enable entries in context menus
Don't show Explorer after volume mounting
Restore hidden dialog boxes
 Hide the following drives in Explorer: 
Save Parameters...
with TEMP Environment Variables
OK
Cancel
These changes will take effect#only after restarting Windows!


[RamDiskUI]
 RamDisk Configuration Tool 
OK
Exit

Basic
    Size:
KB
MB
GB
Allocate Memory Dynamically
    Drive Letter:
Unmount
    File System:
Launch at Windows Startup
Create TEMP Folder
Set TEMP Variables...
Min: %d %s
Max: %d %s
Instead of allocating the whole size, memory is#allocated only when it is actually used.#This is slower but can save a lot of memory if#you are using only a small part of the ramdisk.
Unmount the selected AIM drive and unregister it.
Default: NTFS.##*FAT* file systems are usually faster but with less features.#FAT and FAT32 also have limitations in the maximal volume size.
Once created, register the ramdisk to be started with Windows.#Several ramdisks can be registered.
Create a Temp folder at the root of the volume.##To create other folders, define what you want in a#folder of your hard drive, and specify it in the Data tab.

Advanced
Cluster Size:
Drive Label:
Quick Format
Enable NTFS Compression
Removable media
Use 4KB Sector Size
Dynamic RamDisk Parameters...
 Memory Type: 
Virtual
AWE
Large-page
Use Mount Point:
Unmount
Run after mounting:
Default
0.5 KB
1 KB
2 KB
4 KB
8 KB
16 KB
32 KB
64 KB
Bigger clusters are usually faster but can use more#disk space, especially with a large number of files.
Label size is limited by the file system:#32 characters with NTFS, 11 with *FAT*.
Default: disabled.##Do a quick format. It can speed up the RamDisk building but the allocated#memory does not immediately appear as used in the Windows Task Manager.
Default: disabled.##Allows files to be compressed before being written to the ramdisk.#Only works with the NTFS file system.#Do not use it if you care about speed!##Not recommended with dynamic ramdisks, because memory#may not be released properly.
Default: disabled.##Ramdisk is created as a removable media.#The "Eject" option dismounts the ramdisk.#Data are usually flushed to the disk without delay.
Default: Virtual##Virtual is the fastest.#AWE and Large-page are guaranteed to be never written to the pagefile.##Large-page is only available for dynamic memory allocation. Faster than AWE but#allocations can sometimes slow down the system because of RAM fragmentation.#Disabled on systems with buggy implementation.
Default: disabled.##Use a folder instead of a drive letter to mount the ramdisk.
Unmount selected AIM mount point and unregister it.
The mount point must be an empty directory located on a NTFS volume.#Up to 10 mount points can be registered to be mounted at Windows startup.
Once the volume is ready (formatted and data copied), run the specified file.#It can be an executable or a command file.#The file runs in session 0 ("System" user), which means that no window will#be displayed.

Data
Load Content from Image File or Folder:
Synchronize at System Shutdown
Copy only files with Archive attribute
Delete data removed from the RamDisk
Excluded Folders:
Synchronize now
If you select a folder, its entire content will be copied once the ramdisk#created, with file attributes and ACL, depending on the file system.##An image file must be raw, without partition, and with a valid file system.#Such image can be created for instance with a right click on a drive letter#in Explorer: "Save disk contents as image file".
Default: disabled.##Copy data from the ramdisk to the folder or image file at#system shutdown, depending on the parameters below.
One folder per line.#Folders are relative to the root of the ramdisk#(drive letter or mount point): do not add it.
Synchronize all the registered ramdisks now.

Using physical memory with dynamic ramdisks requires the privilege to lock pages in memory in the local group policy.#If you choose to continue, this privilege will be granted for the Administrators group.##Do you want to continue?
Privilege granted successfully.#A logout is required for this change to take effect.#Logout now?
Error: cannot grant the privilege.

Ready
Starting processing...
Error: size must be at least %d KB.
Error: size must not exceed %d %cB.
Error: incorrect size.
Error: no empty folder selected.
The selected mount point will be unmounted.#Any unsaved data will be lost.#Continue?
Unmounting selected mount point...
This volume will be unmounted.#Any unsaved data will be lost.#Continue?
Unmounting current volume...
Error: the volume cannot be unmounted.
Mounting new RamDisk...
Error: disk cannot be created.
Error: cannot find volume.
Error: the file does not contain a valid file system.
Error: the volume cannot be formatted.
Error: the volume cannot be mounted.
Copying files...
Error: files cannot be copied.
Run user command...
Error: cannot run user command.
Displaying new drive...
Saving parameters...
Warning: too many mount points.#This one will not be registered.
Error: cannot create service.
Done.
Unmounting volume...
Synchronizing...

Use Temp Variables
User:
System:
Set All To:
Use a Junction
from:
to:
Set Defaults
OK
Cancel
Error: cannot create junction.

Memory Release Method:
Automatic
TRIM Commands
Free Space Wiping
 Free Space Wiping Parameters 
These parameters are ignored when TRIM commands are used.
Minimal Amount of Data to Clean:
Minimal Time between 2 Cleanups:
Maximal Activity before Cleanup:
Seconds
MB/s
Size of Allocated Memory Blocks:
OK
Cancel
"Automatic" uses TRIM commands when available. They are much#more efficient but they require NTFS and Windows 7 or later.##Otherwise, when required, depending on the 3 parameters below, a#cleanup function wipes the whole empty space with a temporary file#filled with 0 (because data blocks filled with 0 are automatically freed).
Default: 20.##Number of bytes per allocated memory block, in power of 2.#The minimal value is 12 (4 KB). Use 13 for 8 KB, 14 for 16 KB,#and so on, up to 30 (1 GB).##A lower value can reduce the memory use and improve#efficiency of the cleanup function in case of highly#fragmented files, but it also reduces the performances.
Default: 10.##The cleanup function runs only if this amount of memory can#be freed. The value is a ratio of the total drive space (e.g.:#10/1000 of a 4 GB drive = 40 MB). This is only an estimate: the#memory amount actually freed can be slightly higher or lower.
Default: 10.##A low value can make the cleanup more responsive but may be inappropriate#in case where files are regularly deleted without being recreated.
Default: 10.##Wait until reads and writes are below this value before processing the cleanup.

Warning: the fast startup feature of Windows is enabled. This can lead to some issues:##● The system writes the ramdisk content onto the hard drive at shutdown, and restores it at startup.#● The data synchronization feature of AIM Toolkit does not work at system shutdown.##Open the Shutdown settings to disable the fast startup.
Shutdown settings
Do not show this warning again
Close


[MountImg]
 Mount New Virtual Disk 
Image File:
Drive Letter
Mount Point
Unmount
Device Type:
Hard Disk
CD/DVD
Read-only
Removable
Mount at Windows Startup
OK
Cancel
Mounting...
AIM - Mount Point
Unregisters the selected image file from Windows startup,#and then unmounts the selected drive or mount point.
Enter image file name, select it with the "..." button#or drag and drop it.#A wrong extension can make the mouting fail!##If the file does not exist, you will be prompted to#create a new raw file.##The drop-down list displays the files registered to#be mounted at Windows startup.
The mount point must be an empty directory located on a NTFS volume.##If you drag and drop a folder, it will be selected as mount point.
"CD/DVD" is recommended for ISO, BIN and NRG files,#"Hard Disk" for other formats.
Prevent writing to the image file.
This usually disables the write caching: the data#are immediately written to the image file but#this can decrease the performances.
Registers the image file and parameters#to be mounted at Windows startup.

An error occurred while the mounting.#Please check the parameters.
Error: file system of the selected mount point does not support reparse points.
The selected directory is already a mount point.#If you choose to continue, the previously mounted volume will become unreachable via this mount point.##Do you still want to continue?
Error: the selected mount point is not an empty directory.
Error: the selected drive letter is already in use.
Error: cannot create service.

Create New Image File
The file does not exist.#Do you want to create a new RAW image file?
        File Size:
Mount
Create
Cancel
Error: file cannot be created.
Error: cannot create a file of the specified size.

Bytes
KB
MB
GB
TB
PB


[AIMtk-Dlg]
Warning: you don't have enough rights to properly dismount this volume.#The write buffers might not be flushed and therefore there is a risk of data loss.##Do you still want to continue?
The volume is in use by another process and cannot be locked.##If all your data are saved, you can safely continue and the volume will be properly dismounted.##Do you want to continue?
The virtual disk has been modified.##Do you want to save it as an image file before removing it?
Do not show this warning again
Do not ask again
OK
Cancel
Yes
No
Opening device...
Notifying applications about device removal...
Flushing file buffers...
Locking volume...
Dismounting file system...
Saving image file...
Removing device...
Removing mount point...
Cannot open device.
%s is not an AIM virtual disk.
Cannot remove device.
Cannot remove mount point.

 Save Disk Image 
Image File:
OK
Cancel
ISO Images
All Files
%s locked and ready.
%s is in use by another process and cannot be locked.#Therefore, it can be modified while copying.
Save of %s in progress... %S
Volume %s successfully saved into %s.
Unsupported drive type.
Error retrieving volume properties.
